Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
- Box: 51, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 26: The Trade Unions in Switzerland, 1947; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: Eduard Weckerle
    Notes: September 1947
  - Item 27: Trade Union Organisation and Industrial Relations in Trinidad, 1947; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: F.W. Dalley
  - Item 28: Stop Union Raiding, 1962; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: William Kashtan
- Box: 51, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Organization of Labor in Philadelphia, 1940; Publication (Box 51, Folder 15)
    Author: Edgar Barclay Cale
- Box: 51, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Major Labor Federations in the Philippines, Publication (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Box: 51, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Labor Looks at Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 51, Folder 17)
    Author: Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions
  - Item 2: Labor Unions and the Defense Job, 1951; Publication (Box 51, Folder 17)
    Notes: March 1951
  - Item 3: Where Union Members Stand on 1958 Demands, Publication (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: A Labor Union "Bill of Rights", 1958; Publication (Box 51, Folder 17)
    Author: American Civil Liberties Union
    Notes: September 1958
  - Item 5: Labor Policy and National Defense, 1941; Publication (Box 51, Folder 17)
    Author: Seaview Country Club
    Notes: May 9-11, 1941
  - Item 6: The Trade Unions: Organisation and Action, Publication (Box 51, Folder 17)
    Author: J.T. Murphy, John W. Muir, William Graham
  - Item 7: Labor's 1955 Demands, Publication (Box 51, Folder 17)
    Notes: March 1955
- Box: 51, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Trade Unionism and the Economic Future of South Africa, 1968; Publication (Box 51, Folder 18)
    Author: J.A. Grobbelaar
    Notes: July 1968
- Box: 51, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions and Full Employment, 1953; Publication (Box 51, Folder 19)
    Author: Swedish Confederation of Trade Unions
  - Item 2: Trade Union Educational Work, 1969; Publication (Box 51, Folder 19)
    Author: B. Viklund
  - Item 3: Working Environment, Publication (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Box: 51, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Democracy in Trade Unions, 1946; Publication (Box 51, Folder 20)
    Notes: March 1946
  - Item 2: Democracy in Trade Unions, 1943; Publication (Box 51, Folder 20)
    Notes: November 1943
  - Item 3: Labor Unions and the Public Interest, 1950; Publication (Box 51, Folder 20)
    Notes: June 1950
  - Item 4: The Postwar Role of Labor Unions, 1945; Publication (Box 51, Folder 20)
    Notes: August 1945
  - Item 5: Democracy in Trade Unions, 1943; Publication (Box 51, Folder 20)
- Box: 51, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Danger Signals for Organised Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 51, Folder 21)
    Author: William Z. Foster
    Notes: August 1953
  - Item 2: A Labor Party for the United States, Publication (Box 51, Folder 21)
    Author: The Social Economic Foundation, Inc.
  - Item 3: The Trade Union Movement and the Government, Publication (Box 51, Folder 21)
    Author: George Woodcock
  - Item 4: Trade Unions and Politics, Publication (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Labour in Transition, Publication (Box 51, Folder 21)
    Author: John Burton
  - Item 6: Labor Unions in Politics, 1956; Publication (Box 51, Folder 21)
    Notes: March 1956
- Box: 51, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions in Sweden, Publication (Box 51, Folder 22)
    Author: Tiden-Barnangen
  - Item 2: On International Relations and Contemporary Trade Union Movement, 1965; Publication (Box 51, Folder 22)
    Author: Confederation of Trade Unions of Yugoslavia
  - Item 3: The Ministry of Labor and the General Confederation of Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 51, Folder 22)
    Author: Argentine Departmento de Biblioteca
  - Item 4: Der Blockierte "Transmissionsriemen", 1969; Publication (Box 51, Folder 22)
    Author: Wolf Oschlies
  - Item 5: Labor and Political Parties in Latin America: Three Examples, Publication (Box 51, Folder 22)
    Author: John J. Crowley
- Box: 51, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Labor Money in Wisconsin Politics, Publication (Box 51, Folder 23)
    Author: H. Gaylon Greenhill
- Box: 51, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Union Membership in Puerto Rico in June 1970, Publication (Box 51, Folder 24)
    Author: Ruben A. Vilches
- Box: 51, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Regulation of Labor Unions, 1937; Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    Author: Walter Gordon Merritt
    Notes: March 1937
  - Item 2: Labor Unions Under the Taft-Hartley Law, 1948; Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    Author: Opinion Research Research Corporation
    Notes: April 1948
  - Item 3: Shall Trade Unions be Regulated by Law?, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    Author: Samuel Untermeyer, Morris Hillquit
  - Item 4: Report on Certain Aspects of Labor Union Reponsibility and Control, Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    Author: The City Club of New York
  - Item 5: The Demand for Regulation of Labor Unions, 1938; Publication (Box 51, Folder 25)
    Author: International Juridical Association
- Box: 52, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Guide for Union Officers Maintaining Union Records, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: A Guide for Union Officers Maintaining Union Records, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Box: 52, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions and the Law, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
    Author: Henry Strauss
- Box: 52, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions and Trade Disputes, 1965; Publication (Box 52, Folder 3)
    Author: Republic of Zambia
- Box: 52, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor Unions and the Concept of Public Service, Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
    Author: Roscoe Pound
- Box: 52, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Democracy in Labor Unions, Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Author: University of Buffalo
  - Item 2: Labor and the Public, Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Author: Maxwell S. Stewart
  - Item 3: Trade Unions and the Individual in English Law, Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Author: Cyril Grunfeld
  - Item 4: Spotlight on Union Activities, 1958; Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Author: National Association of Manufacturers
    Notes: January 1958
  - Item 5: Trade Union Rights, 1949; Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Notes: July 14, 1949
  - Item 6: Report on Certain Aspects of Labor Union Responsibility and Control, Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Union Rights, Activities, and Responsibilities, 1948; Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Notes: October 1948
  - Item 8: Cuvintare la Congresul Uniunii Generale a Sindicatelor din Romania, 1971; Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Author: Nicolae Ceausescu
    Notes: March 23, 1971
    Language: Romanian.
- Box: 52, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Journey to the Soviet Trade Unions, 1965; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Author: Charles R. Allen
  - Item 2: Labor Unions- Russia, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Author: Kotikov
  - Item 3: Planirovamic Raboty Frofsivznogo Komitita, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Author: Klavdiia Pavlovria Mishna
  - Item 4: Organizatsiia Raboty Profgrvpy, 1967; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Author: Nina Aleksandrovna Nedosekina
  - Item 5: Povyshenie Roli Profsoiuzov v Period Stroitel'stva Kommunizma, 1967; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Author: Ivanov
  - Item 6: Soviet Trade Unions, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Author: Novosti Press Agency Publishing House
  - Item 7: Trade Unions of Our Soviet Ally, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Author: Clifford T. McAvoy
  - Item 8: The Role of Trade Unions in the State, Economic and Cultural Life of the U.S.S.R., 1960; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Author: N. Antropov
  - Item 9: Trade Unions and Industrial Relations in the Soviet Union, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Author: Maria Feingold
- Box: 52, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Russian Trade Unions, 1961; Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
    Author: I. Borshchenko
- Box: 52, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: South African Trade Unionism, Publication (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Box: 52, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Recent Discussions of Union Democracy, 1961; Publication (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Author: Princeton University
    Notes: July 1961
- Box: 52, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Union Constitutions, Publication (Box 52, Folder 10)
    Author: Leo Bromwich
- Box: 52, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Unions and Union Leaders of Their Own Choosing, Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
    Author: Clark Kerr
  - Item 2: Union Government and Administration Course Outline, 1947; Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
    Notes: May 1947
  - Item 3: Local Convention Representation and Constitutional Amendments in National Unions, Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Trusteeship, Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Local Union Election Appeals, Publication (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Box: 52, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Role of International Unionism in Canada, Publication (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Trade Union Organization, Publication (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Planning, 1946; Publication (Box 52, Folder 12)
    Notes: May 10, 1946
- Box: 52, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions in Sweden, 1961; Publication (Box 52, Folder 13)
    Author: Tiden- Barnangen
- Box: 52, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Popular Movements in Sweden, Publication (Box 52, Folder 14)
    Author: Albin Lind
- Box: 52, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Proposals of the Tanzania Government on the Recommendations of the Presidential Commission of Enquiry into the National Union of Tanganyika Workers, 1967; Publication (Box 52, Folder 15)
    Author: Tanzania Government
- Box: 52, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions in Developing Countries, 1966; Publication (Box 52, Folder 16)
    Author: Sven Fockstedt
- Box: 52, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Les Syndicats Americains Dans un Tournant, Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
    Author: Les Editions Syndicalistes
  - Item 2: The Labor Movement in the United States, 1962; Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
    Author: Jack Barbash
    Notes: March 1962
  - Item 3: Economic Implications of Union Power, 1962; Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Labor and the American Way, 1960; Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
    Author: Starr
  - Item 5: Union Economic Power and the Public Interest, Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
    Author: The Society of Business Advisory Professions, Inc.
  - Item 6: What Organized Labor Expects of Management, Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
    Author: George Meany
  - Item 7: 8 Steps for Keeping Unions Out, 1963; Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
    Author: Commercial Car Journal
    Notes: August 1963
  - Item 8: Organized Labor in an "Employeeistic" Society, 1964; Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
    Author: Stanley Young
  - Item 9: Two Views of American Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 52, Folder 17)
    Author: Frances Perkins, J. Paul St. Sure
- Box: 52, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Democracy in Trade Unions, 1944; Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Notes: November 1944
  - Item 2: A Cross Section of American Opinion on the Need for Regulation of Labor Unions, Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Author: Lexington Avenue Civic Association
  - Item 3: Report on Certain Aspects of Labor Union Responsibility and Control, Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: The Forward March of American Labor, Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Author: League for Industrial Democracy
  - Item 5: Democracy in Labor Unions, 1952; Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Notes: June 1952
  - Item 6: Labor Unions and the Future, 1946; Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Notes: August 1946
  - Item 7: Labor Unions, Our Hope or Our Despair, 1923; Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Author: The Fellowship Press, Inc.
    Notes: February 1923
  - Item 8: Where is Organized Labor Going?, 1949; Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Author: Donald R. Richberg
    Notes: Autumn 1949
  - Item 9: Labor's 1959 Bid for Power, Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Notes: January 1959
  - Item 10: The Story of American Labor, 1952; Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Author: Oregon State Federation of Labor
  - Item 11: Forces Shaping the Decline of Labor Union Power, 1960; Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Notes: August 1960
  - Item 12: Labor and the American Way, Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Author: Mark Starr
  - Item 13: Current Anti-Labor Activities, 1938; Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Author: David J. Saposs
    Notes: April 11, 1938
  - Item 14: Labor Union "Bill of Rights", Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Item 15: Monopoly Power, Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: Labor Monopoly, Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Author: Leo Wolfman
  - Item 17: Forces Shaping the Decline of Labor Union Power, 1960; Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Item 18: Labor Union Power, 1957; Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Notes: May 1957
  - Item 19: A Manual of Industrial Unionism, 1937; Publication (Box 52, Folder 18)
    Notes: August 1937
- Box: 52, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Demand for Dignity, Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
    Author: C.K. McFarland
  - Item 2: The Rise of Organized Labor, Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
    Author: American Education Publications
  - Item 3: Important Events in American Labor History, Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Danger Ahead for Organized Labor, 1948; Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Danger Signals for Organized Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: The Struggle to Unite, Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
    Author: Irving Brotslaw
  - Item 7: To Build a New World, 1965; Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
    Author: Thomas R. Brooks
  - Item 8: The Trade Labor Movement in the United States, 1962; Publication (Box 52, Folder 19)
    Author: Pennsylvania Department of Public Instruction
    Notes: May 1962
- Box: 52, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Union Membership, 1964; Publication (Box 52, Folder 20)
    Notes: January 1964
  - Item 2: Union Growth Reconsidered, 1961; Publication (Box 52, Folder 20)
    Author: Julius Reezer
- Box: 52, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Statut, 1968; Publication (Box 52, Folder 21)
    Author: Centralni Odbor Sindikata
    Language: Serbian.
  - Item 2: Why the Trade Unions Have Been Re-Organized, 1964; Publication (Box 52, Folder 21)
    Author: Beogradski Graficki Zavod
  - Item 3: Socio-Economic Scope of Yugoslav Trade Union Action, 1964; Publication (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Materijalna Osnova Kulture I Uloga Radnih Organizacija I Sindikatat U Kulturnom Zivotu Radnika, Publication (Box 52, Folder 21)
    Author: Urednistvo I Administracija
  - Item 5: Trade Unionism in Yugoslavia, Publication (Box 52, Folder 21)
- Box: 52, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Power of Choice, Publication (Box 52, Folder 22)
- Box: 52, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Radical Labor in the Nevada Mining Booms, 1961; Publication (Box 52, Folder 23)
    Author: Russell R. Elliott
- Box: 52, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Impact of Land Reform on Economic and Social Development, 1965; Publication (Box 52, Folder 24)
    Notes: March 10, 1965
- Box: 52, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Opinion Publica Acerca de la Reforma Agraria, 1965; Publication (Box 52, Folder 25)
    Author: Universidad de los Andes
- Box: 52, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Governor Landon vs. Candidate Landon, Publication (Box 52, Folder 26)
    Author: Democratic National Campaign Committee
- Box: 52, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Community Influentials in a Middle-Sized City, Publication (Box 52, Folder 27)
    Author: William H. Form, Warren L. Sauer
- Box: 52, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Latin American Seminar, 1960; Publication (Box 52, Folder 28)
    Author: National Science Foundation
- Box: 52, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: South America, 1960; Publication (Box 52, Folder 29)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Foreign Relations
    Notes: February 20, 1960
  - Item 2: Economic Developments in South America, 1962; Publication (Box 52, Folder 29)
    Author: U.S. Joint Economic Committee
  - Item 3: Cooperation for Progress in Latin America, 1961; Publication (Box 52, Folder 29)
    Author: Committee for Economic Development
    Notes: April 1961
  - Item 4: Towards a Dynamic Development Policy for Latin America, 1963; Publication (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Invisible Hands in Inflation and Growth, 1965; Publication (Box 52, Folder 29)
    Author: Joseph Grunwald
  - Item 6: Seven Years of the Alliance for Progress, Publication (Box 52, Folder 29)
    Author: U.S. Agency for Industrial Development
  - Item 7: Latin America, 1958; Publication (Box 52, Folder 29)
    Author: A.G. Mezerik
    Notes: November 1958
- Box: 52, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Economic Policies and Programs in Middle America, 1963; Publication (Box 52, Folder 30)
- Box: 52, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: People for Progress, 1970; Publication (Box 52, Folder 31)
    Language: English; Spanish.
- Box: 52, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Seminar on Industrial Programming, 1963; Publication (Box 52, Folder 32)
    Notes: March 4-15, 1963
- Box: 52, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Latin American Panorama, 1966; Publication (Box 52, Folder 33)
    Author: Ronald M. Schneider
- Box: 52, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: La Izquierda Democratica Latinoamericana en la Doctrina y en la Practica: Apra y Accion Democratica, 1968; Publication (Box 52, Folder 34)
    Author: Efren Cordova
- Box: 52, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Social and Labor Problems of Peru and Uruguay, Publication (Box 52, Folder 35)
    Author: Mary M. Cannon
  - Item 2: Una Hipotesis Sociologica Acerca de la Integracion Latinoamericana, 1965; Publication (Box 52, Folder 35)
    Author: Manuel Barrera Romero
- Box: 52, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Laundry, Cleaning, Dyeing, and Pressing Occupations, 1946; Publication (Box 52, Folder 36)
    Notes: February 1946
- Box: 53, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Summary of Legislative Work, 1951; Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
    Notes: January 3 - October 20, 1951
- Box: 53, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Redundancy, Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
    Author: The Action Society Trust
  - Item 2: Redundancy, Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Layoffs, 1949; Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
    Notes: May 1949
  - Item 4: Handling a Major Curtailment of Work Force, Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Verslag van Collectief Ontslag, Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
    Author: Wetenschappelijk en Scholingsinstituut van het NVV
  - Item 6: Effects of Mass Layoffs on Local Unemployment Rates, 1967; Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
    Author: Kirschner Associates Inc.
  - Item 7: The Impact of Layoff and Recall at Ford-Windsor, Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
    Author: Ontario Economic Council
  - Item 8: Redundancy, Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
    Author: Frank Ware
- Box: 53, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Failure to Report After Layoff, 1961; Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Notes: June 15, 1961
  - Item 2: Discipline for Wildcat Strike, 1962; Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Notes: February 15 1962
  - Item 3: Effect of Compensation Claim, 1961; Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Notes: December 21, 1961
  - Item 4: Refusal to Test Machine, 1961; Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Notes: August 24, 1961
  - Item 5: Sick Leave Misrepresentation, 1961; Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Notes: September 14, 1961
- Box: 53, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Supervision and Leadership, 1927; Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
    Author: Henry C. Metcalf
  - Item 2: Leadership, 1948; Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
    Author: Brehon Somervell
    Notes: April 20, 1948
  - Item 3: Conditions of Effective Leadership in the Industrial Organization, 1944; Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
    Author: Douglas McGregor
    Notes: March-April, 1944
  - Item 4: The Leadership Functions of Executives and Managers, 1962; Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
    Author: Russell H. Ewing
  - Item 5: Organizational Evaluation and Authority, Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
    Author: W. Richard Scott, Sanford M. Dornbusch, Bruce C. Busching, James D. Laing
- Box: 53, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Relationships Among Psychological Differentiation and Leadership Styles as Modified by Relative Masculinity, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
    Author: Leopold Gruenfeld, Jack Arbuthot
  - Item 2: Leadership Style, Confidence in Management and Job Satisfaction, 1966; Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
    Author: P.J. Sadler
- Box: 53, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Leadership Needs, Publication (Box 53, Folder 6)
    Author: The Personnel Journal
- Box: 53, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Teaching Effectiveness and the Feedback Mechanism, 1962; Publication (Box 53, Folder 7)
    Author: Wallace Wohlking
    Notes: July 15, 1962
- Box: 53, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Die Dienstverhinderungen Beim Angestellten und ihre Bezahlung, Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
    Author: Betreibs- Kurier
  - Item 2: Federal Employees' Administrative Leave for Hurricane or Severe Weather Conditions, 1966; Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Post Office and Civil Service
    Notes: August 31, 1966
  - Item 3: Federal Employees' Administrative Leave for Hurricane or Severe Weather Conditions, 1967; Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
    Notes: October 17, 1967
  - Item 4: Military Leave Practices, 1962; Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Use of Sick Leave, 1964; Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
    Author: Harold MacDiarmid
  - Item 6: Need for Improved Accounting for Civilian Employees' Leaves of Absence in the Military Departments, 1969; Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
    Author: U.S. General Accounting Office
    Notes: February 7, 1969
  - Item 7: Decision of the Comptroller General of the United States Regarding Administrative Leave to Employees Representing Government Employee Organizations, 1966; Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Post Office and Civil Serviceq
  - Item 8: Teachers' Sabbatical Leave Act, 1965; Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
    Notes: September 2, 1965
  - Item 9: Teachers Sabbatical Leave Program, 1965; Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
    Notes: July 13-14, 1965
  - Item 10: Paid Leave & Leave of Absence Policies, 1975; Publication (Box 53, Folder 8)
    Notes: November 1975
- Box: 53, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 53, Folder 9)